clientattraction.com 2018-08-27

# Privacy Policy | Boldheart

**Privacy Policy**

Boldheart provides information and activities on the Boldheart.com and related websites (the “Site”). Our content includes information about our programs, products and events along with photos, video and educational information for and interactivity with our users and also provides links to other Boldheart sites. While we encourage the interactive nature of our website, we strive to promote the online safety and privacy of our users.

We have implemented this Privacy Policy governing the personally identifiable information (“Personal Consumer Information”) collected by this Site. This Privacy Policy does not govern Personal Consumer Information collected from any other source or in any other manner.

This Privacy Policy is intended to provide you with information as to: (i) the type of information that is collected, (ii) how collected information is used and with whom it is shared; (iii) how we intend to protect the information; and (iv) how you can access, modify and/or delete such information.

We will always respect your privacy, your email address, and the information you give us. We’re not going to sell it, trade it, or abuse any information you submit to us. Here are answers to some common questions you might have regarding this subject.

**How’s my information going to be used?**

When you sign up for our Products or Services, you’ll begin receiving relevant information about Boldheart, invites to our online events, as well as information about programs or products in relevant fields like business growth, education, and personal growth.

**How do I to stop receiving emails from you in the future?**

If you wish to stop receiving emails from us, you may unsubscribe at any time using the link provided at the bottom of all our emails. If after this step you still receive emails from us, there may have been a technical error. Please email our Customer Service at info@boldheart.com, [submit a support ticket here](https://boldheart.zendesk.com/hc/en-us) or call us at (203) 717-4404. We’ll help you out ASAP.

**Who’s going to get my information?**

Your information is safe with us. So don’t worry about getting spam emails. We’ll never give out your email address or any of the information you submit on this site to anyone else.

**What if I email you guys?**

Your emails are confidential, we won’t share your email, data, or email address. It’s just between you and us.

**Do you use cookies?**

Yes, but our cookies don’t contain any personal information. We use them to help you make using our website easier, such as:

To remember your country and language preferences  
To deliver information that matches your interests  
To help us understand our audience and traffic patterns  
To let you automatically log into programs and parts of our site that require membership  
To manage and present site info displayed on our website that will be specific to you

We also use Web Beacons to collect non-personal data on how you use our site, such as how long did you visit our page, what web browser you’re using, what’s your operating system, and who’s your Internet service provider. In addition we also use Google Analytics data and the DoubleClick cookie to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our website. This data is collected from thousands of site visits and analyzed as a whole. This helps us build a better website to match our visitors’ needs.

Web Beacons: We may also place small “tracker gifs” or “beacons” on many of the pages on our website, in online advertising with third parties, and in our emails. We use these beacons, in connection with Cookies, to collect non-personal data on the usage of our site including but not limited to the date and time of the visit, the pages visited, the referring web page, the type of browser (e.g., Internet Explorer, NetScape), the type of operating system (e.g., Windows, Linux, or Mac), and the domain name of the visitor’s Internet service provider (e.g., AOL). This information is collected about thousands of site visits and analyzed as a whole. This information is useful in, for example, tracking the performance of our online advertising such as online banner ads and to determine where to place future advertising on other websites.

Disabling Cookies and Beacons: If you are uncomfortable with the collection of such information through the use of Cookies and Beacons, we recommend disabling these features through your browser preferences, though please understand this will limit the performance and functionality of our Company’s website. Your browser documentation should provide specific procedures for disabling cookie and beacon support.

You may also opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page.](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/)

Or you may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the [Google Analytics Opt-out page](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

**Public forums**

Some parts of our site may enable you to participate in public services such as discussion boards, chats, and live events. Please use discretion when posting personal information about yourself when using these services. Be aware that when you disclose personal information at these sites, such as your name, member name, email address, etc., the information may be collected and used by others to send unsolicited email. The services are open to the public, and what you post there can be seen by anyone and is not protected. We try to moderate the comments as best we can, but we can’t guarantee total control of the comments that you may receive while you participate in these services. Sometimes, you may find other people’s comments to be offensive, harmful or inaccurate. We do our best to monitor our forums and remove any comment, post or thread which we deem to be inappropriate or harmful.

**Our company’s commitment to data security**

We implement a variety of administrative, managerial, and technical security measures to help protect your personal information. Our Company has various internal control standards which relate specifically to the handling of personal information. These include certain controls to help safeguard the information we collect online. Our employees are trained to understand and comply with these controls and we communicate our Privacy Notice, practices and guidelines to our employees. However, while we strive to protect your personal information, you must also take steps to protect your information. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal information while you are on the Internet.

Services and websites we sponsor have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party “hackers” from illegally obtaining this information.

**What if I post in one of your forums or blog posts?**

Occasionally we hold public discussions through forums within our site. This may be on blog posts we put up or in our membership area. Please be aware that this is public space. Use your discretion when you post in our forums and when commenting.

**How adept are you when it comes to data security?**

We have a wide variety of administrative, managerial, and technical security measures put in place to protect your personal information. We’ve never had a breach of security and always strive for excellence in maintaining your privacy.

Do you have more questions? You can contact our Customer Service Team at info@boldheart.com.

**Your privacy is very important to us**

We want to make your experience on the Internet as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and we want you to use the Internet’s vast array of information, tools, and opportunities with complete confidence.

We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how our Company collects information from all end users of our Internet services (the “Services”), including those who access some of our Services but do not have accounts (“Visitors”) and those who may purchase Products and/or pay a monthly service fee to subscribe to the Service (“Members”). This Policy also explains what we do with the information we collect, and the choices Visitors and Members have concerning the collection and use of such information. We request that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.

**Personal Information Our Company Collects And How It Is Used**

**Introduction**

Members may be asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for our Products or Services including name, address, telephone number, billing information (such as a credit card number), and the type of personal computer being used to access the Services. The personal information collected from Members during the registration process (or at any other time) is used primarily to provide a customized experience while using our Products and Services. Your information will never be disclosed, traded, licensed or sold to any third party. However, we may make limited disclosure of personal information under the specific circumstances described below.

The information you provide to us will never be disclosed, traded, licensed or sold to a third party. However, there are specific instances, described below, where your information could be provided to a known third party.

**Login From Integrations:**

For ease of use, you are also given the option to link your Boldheart account on the Site with your account on a third-party site such as, for example, Facebook. The third party site will authenticate your identity, will allow you to log into Boldheart platforms using the single social login buttons, and will share certain personal information that you allow us to collect. By signing-in using your third party identity provider account (“Third Party IdP”), you are authorizing Boldheart to collect, store, and use, in accordance with this Privacy Policy, any and all information that you have authorized the Third Party IdP to provide to Boldheart. Such information may include your first and last name, gender, location, username, email address, picture or phone number.

You will be given the option to link your Boldheart account with your social media account e.g. Facebook. When you choose to login with your social media account the social media site will: authenticate your identity, allow you to log into your Boldheart account using the single social login button, and provide personal information that you agree to share with us. 

Logging in this way means that you give Boldheart authorization to collect, store, and use your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Such information may include your first and last name, gender, location, username, email address, picture, or phone number.

**Third Party Integration**

If you do login through a third party account like Facebook, we share some information with them and they share some information with us but only for purposes of accessing your account. What is shared with us by the third party sites depends on their privacy policy. We would advise that you familiarize yourself with the privacy policy of the third party site to know what information is being shared by them.

When you login to your Boldheart account with your social media account we also share some basic account information with your social media provider. What we share with the social media provider depends on their Privacy Policy. We advise you to check the Privacy Policy of the social media site to familiarize yourself with the information they request from us.

**Affiliate links**

Occasionally you may have clicked on one of Boldheart’s affiliate links and signed up or bought something via that link. In this case, the person or organization in charge of the affiliate link will have the information that you have submitted. This may be your email address, name, address, or whatever else they asked you. If you have signed up for bought something from Boldheart via an affiliate link, please check the privacy policy on their site.

**Online shopping**

If you order services or products directly from our Company we will use the personal information you provide only to process that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

If you complete an order for some other company(ies) that may be linked to our Site, such as an online gift order sent directly to a recipient, you may be asked to provide information about the recipient, such as the recipient’s name, address, and phone number. Our company has no control over the third parties’ use of any personal information you provide when placing such an order. Please exercise care when doing so. We recommend that you familiarize yourself with the Privacy and [Terms of Use](http://boldheart.com/terms-of-use/) policies of any other company(ies) whose web sites you may access from our site.

**Responses to email inquiries**

When Visitors or Members send email inquiries to our company, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. Our company does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party. Thanks for reading our privacy policy.

**Revisions to this policy**

Our Company reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy, our [Terms Of Use & Service agreement](http://boldheart.com/terms-of-use/), and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner, by updating this posting.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on 5/23/2018 and is effective immediately.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy, please send us an email at info@boldheart.com.

**Governing Law**

This Privacy Policy shall be governed by the laws of the State of Connecticut, without regard to its conflict of law provisions. Any dispute concerning this Privacy Policy or your use of this Site shall be submitted to binding arbitration in Connecticut within one (1) year from the date that the cause of action arose (or, if multiple cause of actions are involved, from the date that the first cause of action arose), with such arbitration conducted pursuant to the then prevailing rules of the American Arbitration Association. To the fullest extent permitted by law, no arbitration brought pursuant hereto shall be joined to any other action or any other arbitration initiated pursuant hereto. If any portion of this Privacy Policy is deemed unenforceable, unlawful or void by a Court of competent jurisdiction, then that portion of the Privacy Policy will be deemed severable and will not affect the enforceability or validity of the remaining portions of this Privacy Policy.

Copyright 2010 Boldheart, LLC. All rights reserved.

**Where to direct questions about our privacy policy**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us through the contact information provided on this website.

700 Canal Street, Stamford, CT 06902
